ILR School Alumni News /3066
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Alumni News
1949-1995
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
/3066
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Consists of the "Round Up", the ILR Alumni News, reports, and alumni directories.
8436555
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 19, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 21, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3059: ILR School Press Releases /3060: ILR School Foreign Visitor Information /3061: ILR School Reprints of Articles about the School /3062: ILR School Public Information Center Publications /3063: ILR School Industrial and Labor Relations (ILR) Forum /3065: ILR School Extension Division Records /3069: ILR School Scrapbook /3072 PUBS: ILR School Miscellaneous Publications of the School /3070 mf(d): ILR School Publication "For Our Information" (F.O.I.) Digital from Microfilm /3071: ILR School Albany Extension Division Records
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations -- Periodicals; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Alumni Association; Cornell Industrial and Labor Relations Alumni Association
8436555
- Cornell ILR General (Box 1, Folder 1)
- ILR Alumni Directory (Box 1, Folder 2)
- "Round-Up", 1949 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- "Round-Up", 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- ILR Alumni News, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- ILR Alumni News, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- ILR Alumni News, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- ILR Alumni News, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- ILR Alumni News, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- ILR Alumni News, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- ILR Alumni News, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- ILR Alumni News, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- ILR Alumni News, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- ILR Alumni News, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- ILR Alumni News, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- ILR Alumni News, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- ILR Alumni News, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- ILR Alumni News, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- ILR Alumni News, 1986-1990 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- ILR Alumni Report, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous Alumni Office Documents (Box 1, Folder 21)
- ILR Alumni News (Winter 1991) (Box 1, Folder 22)